ncpa.org 2003-12-09

# National Center for Policy Analysis - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for NCPA Websites

* * *

National Center For Policy Analysis has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for these websites:

www.ncpa.org  
www.mysocialsecurity.org  
www.debate-central.org  
www.womenintheeconomy.org  
www.teamncpa.org

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We will not sell, reveal or share your personal information. 

Our sites' registration forms require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The user's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our sites contain links to other sites. www.ncpa.org, www.mysocialsecurity.org, www.debate-central.org, and www.womenintheeconomy.org are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

Our sites use order forms for users to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's financial information (like their account or credit card numbers) and contact information (like their email address). Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Contact information that is collected is used to send orders and information about our organization to our users. The user's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Our online surveys sometimes ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our sites, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send information about our organization to our visitors. The user's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Security

These sites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Choice/Opt-Out

Our sites provide users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

Users can request the removal of their information from our database by sending an email to [ncpa@ncpa.org](mailto:ncpa@ncpa.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20-%20Choice/Opt-Out). This will stop future communications and service from the NCPA. 

Contacting Online Services

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of these sites, or your dealings with them, you can contact:

Rick Smith   
National Center For Policy Analysis   
12655 N. Central Expy. - Suite 720   
Dallas, TX 75243-1739   

| 

* * *

12655 N. Central Expy., Suite 720 - Dallas, TX 75243-1739 - 972/386-6272 - Fax 972/386-0924  
655 15th St. N.W., Suite 375 - Washington, DC 20005 - 202/628-6671 - Fax 202/628-6474  
Copyright © 2002 National Center for Policy Analysis - All rights reserved.
